{
    "id": "1b8e6dd5f70148ddba381fd946568d8a",
    "title": "The positive, comparative and superlative degrees",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2b49fc9cba3f47959b9baf8984c5ff8a",
            "title": "The Positive, Comparative And Superlative Degree",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How is your mother today? Is she any …………………………..?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "better",
                        "best"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In India May is …………………………… than June.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hot",
                        "hotter",
                        "hottest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julie is ………………………….. than her sister.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "pretty",
                        "prettier",
                        "prettiest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the ………………………… girl in your class?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "beautiful",
                        "most beautiful",
                        "more beautiful"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which is the ………………………….. of all metals.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "precious",
                        "more precious",
                        "most precious"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her husband is ten years ……………………………… than her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "old",
                        "older",
                        "oldest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "All of us are bad singers, but I sing the ………………………….. of all.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bad",
                        "worse",
                        "worst"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think you require a ………………………….. diet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "nutritious",
                        "more nutritious",
                        "most nutritious"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which is the ………………………… part of India?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "dry",
                        "drier",
                        "driest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was the ……………………….. moment of my life.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "proud",
                        "prouder",
                        "proudest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}